Mother, please, come in my heart.
母親啊，請降臨於我心。
Clean my heart, so you are there. O put Your feet into my heart.
淨化我心，祢便存在於此。噢，請將祢的蓮足放在我心。
let Your feet be worshiped there.
讓我從心膜拜祢的蓮足。
For the first time Shri Adi Shakti Mataji Shri Nirmala Devi travels to the Heart of the Universe.
太初之母錫呂瑪塔吉首次親臨宇宙之心。
Beginning Her auspicious journey in Mumbai, India (the 'Yoga-bhumi', the land of yoga and the Kundalini of the Universe),
這趟吉祥的旅程始於印度孟買 - 「瑜伽之鄉」，連結與宇宙昆達里尼的發源地，
where a small group of local yogis gather to wish their fond farewells, knowing that early the next morning
當地一小群霎哈嘉瑜珈士齊聚一堂，懷著依依不捨之情道別，因為他們知道隔天一早
on the 1st January 1974, Shri Mataji will land by aeroplane in London, the Heart of the Heart.
1974 年 1 月 1 日，錫呂瑪塔吉將乘機降臨倫敦，這「心中的心」。
'England will be Jerusalem.
『英格蘭將成為耶路撒冷。
Remember that I've come all the way from India to do that.
記得我千里迢迢從印度就是來完成這事件。
Let's see how the English are going to behave towards it'.
讓我們看看英國人對此會有甚麼反應。
Nearly 2,000 years since Shri Mataji last walked in England as Mother Mary with Her son, the youthful Jesus;
距離錫呂瑪塔吉以聖母瑪利亞的身份與年輕的耶穌最後一次在英格蘭行走，已時隔近兩千年；
150 years since the incarnation of Shri Bhairavanath as William Blake;
距離錫呂·巴爾伐納特的降世威廉·布萊克，已過去一百五十年；
and thousands of years since Shri Adi Guru Dattatreya (as had Shri Ganesha before him) meditated along the banks of the River Thames.
距離太初導師錫呂·達陀陀哩耶（如同之前的格泥沙）在泰晤士河畔冥想，也已過去數千年。
'He predicted it one hundred years back, and today if you come to Sahaja Yoga, you'll be amazed what you are.
『他在一百年前就預言了這一切，而現在當你來到霎哈嘉瑜伽，你會對"真我"的真實身分感到驚嘆不已。』
Whatever he has predicted about England being the Jerusalem of tomorrow, that tomorrow is today.
他預言英格蘭將成為明日的耶路撒冷——而那個明日，就是今天。
The place of worship, where people have to come to worship'.
『這將是人們必須前來朝聖的聖地。』
O Holy Virgin,
至聖聖母啊，
clad in purest white,
身披最純淨的白衣，
Unlock heaven's golden gates
開啟天國的金色大門
Salutations to the Goddess who abides in Wales, 'Cymru', the land of the Kundalini power,
向駐守於威爾斯——「西姆魯」這片昆達里尼力量之地的女神致敬
of Shri Gauri Kundalini Mata - the Maharashtra of Britain and the land of the Goddess Rhiannon,
聖女哥維,昆達里尼母親的聖地－不列顛的馬哈拉施特拉與女神里安農的領土，
who rides the pure white horse of the Kundalini. We worship Mount Snowdon, 'Yr Wyddfa',
她駕馭著昆達里尼的純白駿馬。我們崇敬雪墩山，「厄爾威德法」，
the seat of that Kundalini power, drawing the water element from the ocean as purifying rain.
昆達里尼力量的聖座，從海洋汲取水元素轉化為淨化之雨。
We honour the holy Isle of Anglesey, 'Ynys Môn', the intersection of numerous nadis and ley lines in the Mother Earth,
我們尊崇神聖的安格爾西島，「恩尼斯蒙」，大地之母眾多脈輪與能量線的交匯處。
and the central point within the British Isles;
以及大不列顛群島的中心點
land of abundant fertility and last stronghold of the Druids who worshiped Shri Adi Guru Dattatreya;
肥沃豐饒之地，也是德魯伊教徒崇拜太初導師錫呂·達陀陀哩耶最後的堡壘
with its Swayambhuh to Shri Ganesha at Holyhead, 'Caergybi', guarding towards the west.
聖石象神格泥沙位於神首(威爾斯語：Caergybi)，鎮守西方門戶
and the great River Severn, 'Afon Hafren', one of the seven great nadis of Britain, winding from the Plynlimon mountains in the West,
以及偉大的塞文河（威爾斯語：Afon Hafren），這條不列顛七大納迪河流之一，自西部普林利蒙山脈蜿蜒而下
towards the Bristol channel, the Vishuddhi of Britain and the wide Atlantic Ocean.
朝著布里斯托灣方向，英國與遼闊的大西洋的喉輪所在。
Wales: land of song, rivers and mountains.
威爾斯：歌曲、河流與山巒之地。
Salutations to the Goddess who abides in Ireland, 'Éire', the land of the Goddess 'Ériu', the land of the Devi,
向居於愛爾蘭的女神致敬，'埃爾'是女神'埃黎歐'的領地，也是女神之土，
the Centre Heart chakra of Shri Jagadamba, of Shri Durga Mata, who took the form of a blessed cow,
這裡是聖母女神傑格丹巴、⺟親杜伽的中心輪，她曾降世為一頭祥瑞的母牛，
Shri Gomata, along the banks of the River Boyne, 'Abhainn na Bóinne';
⺟親神⽜，佇立於博因河畔，即「阿布海寧·那·博因內」；
who as the Paps of Anu, 'Dá Chích Anann',
她以阿努之乳「達·奇奇·阿南」的姿態示現，
grants all the sustenance of the Mother Goddess from Her all-embracing love for the world with Her nourishing breasts;
以其滋養萬物的胸懷，從母神無盡之愛中賜予世間所有生養之恩；
and who manifested as Bridgid of the flame, the Celtic Goddess Brigid,
並以火焰化身布里吉德顯現，即凱爾特女神布里吉德
at the Hill of Uisneach, the place of the hearth, and the Sacred Centre of Ireland,
在烏石納赫山丘，愛爾蘭的中心之處。
from where, on 1st February each year, they light the beacons to enlighten all the thirty-two counties of Ireland
每年二月一日，他們從此處點燃火把，照亮愛爾蘭三十二郡，
with the light of the Triple Goddess of the Sun, Brigid, the Celtic Athena,
藉著太陽三重女神布里吉德的光芒，這位凱爾特的雅典娜，
the Irish goddess of spring fertility and life of the Arts crafts and the spirit of prophecy.
她是愛爾蘭的春之女神，孕育生命、藝術工藝與預言靈感之源。
We salute the Swayambhus at Skellig Michael, 'Sceilig Mhichíl', to the southwest and at Ireland’s Eye, 'Inis Mac Neasáin', in the East,
我們向斯凱利格·麥克爾島（'Sceilig Mhichíl'）西南方的自生者們致敬，也向東部的愛爾蘭之眼島（'Inis Mac Neasáin'）致意，
and the seven hills of Dublin, 'Baile Átha Cliath', and the seven hills of Belfast, 'Béal Feirste'.
以及都柏林（'Baile Átha Cliath'）的七座山丘，和貝爾法斯特（'Béal Feirste'）的七座山丘。
We bow to the great River Shannon, 'Abhainn na Sionainne', the longest river of the British Isles, which flows from Shannon Pot in the Cuilcagh Mountains,
我們向偉大的香農河（'Abhainn na Sionainne'）鞠躬致意，這條不列顛群島最長的河流從北愛爾蘭阿爾斯特地區（'Ulaidh'）邊境附近
'Binn Chuilceach', near the border with Ulster, 'Ulaidh', in Northern Ireland
奎爾卡山脈（'Binn Chuilceach'）的香農泉發源
to flow southerly through Loch Aillionn,
向南流經艾利恩湖，
Loch Rí and Loch Deirgeirt,
再經過里湖與迪爾格特湖，
through the to the cities of Athlone, 'Baile Átha Luain', and Limerick, 'Luimneach',
途經阿斯隆市「巴利阿萨卢安」與利默里克「盧姆尼亞克」，
and into the Shannon Estuary, to the place where in the mid-1980s, Shri Mataji's feet touched the land of Ireland
最終注入香農河口——這裡正是 1980 年代中期錫呂瑪塔吉雙足踏上愛爾蘭土地之地
for the one and only time, at Shannon Airport en route to America.
此生僅此一次，在香農機場轉機前往美國途中。
'England itself is really a great country - it's the Heart of the Universe, is the greatest country
'英格蘭本身確實是個偉大的國家——它是宇宙之心，是最偉大的國度，
as far as the articulation is concerned; and the source of all that is good, comes from this country'.
就其文明表達而言；世間一切良善的源頭，皆源自這片土地。
Salutations to the Goddess who abides in England, the land of Shri Shiva, the pure Spirit,
敬禮棲居英格蘭的女神，此乃聖濕婆淨土，純粹靈性之所
the left heart, the pure white land of Albion, of William Blake,
左側心臟，威廉·布萊克筆下純淨的白土亞爾比恩，
as expressed by the evocative white cliffs of Dover, the land where the Goddess Herself abides as purity and chastity.
正如多佛那引人遐思的白色懸崖所展現，這片土地是女神以純潔與貞節之姿駐留之所。
'Now, heart is the most important organ in the body, if the heart fails, the whole body fails.
『心臟是人體最重要的器官，若心臟衰竭，全身便隨之衰敗。
Supposing the brain fails, still the body will go on,
即便大腦機能喪失，軀體仍可持續運作，
but if the heart fails, the body stops functioning.
但若心臟停止跳動，身體機能便會終止。
So the attack is on the heart.
所以敵人的攻擊目標就是心臟。
All the satanic forces and demonic forces and destructive forces
所有邪惡勢力、魔鬼力量與破壞力量
will try to attack the heart naturally, because if they attack any other place
自然都會試圖攻擊心臟，因為打擊任何其他部位
then the body will be still functioning.
身體仍將繼續運作。
So first, they will try all their methods to attack the heart'.
所以首先，他們會用盡一切方法來攻擊心臟。
We invoke Shri Shiva as Shri Nad’īshwara, the Lord of rivers, the channels,
我們呼喚濕婆(全能主)作為 輪脈之主，河流之主，通道之主，
to vibrate the nadis of England and to awaken the people of this land of Albion from spiritual sleep.
啟迪英格蘭的經絡，並喚醒這片阿爾比恩土地上的人們，從靈性沉睡中覺醒。
'The River Thames has to become the Ganges. This is the Heart of the Universe, England is the Heart'.
泰晤士河必須成為恆河。此乃宇宙之心，英格蘭即為心臟所在。
First with Shri Mataji at Seven Springs in Gloucestershire, the source of the Thames in the Cotswold Hills:
最初錫呂瑪塔吉在格洛斯特郡的七泉，泰晤士河的源頭科茲窩丘陵：
from the Sanskrit Tamas, the Ida nadi that flows through the Heart of the Universe and purifies this universe.
泰晤源自梵語「Tamas」，即流經宇宙之心的左脈，淨化這個宇宙。
We worship the seven rivers, the the Sapta Nadis of the Heart:
我們崇敬七條聖河，即心輪的七脈：薩普塔納迪。
the Thames;
泰晤士河；
the Derwent in Yorkshire;
約克郡的德文特河；
the Trent in Derbyishire;
德比郡的特倫特河；
the Ouse in Cambridgeshire;
劍橋郡的烏斯河；
the Don in Aberdeenshire, Scotland;
蘇格蘭亞伯丁郡的頓河；
the Forth in Stirling, Scotland;
蘇格蘭斯特靈的福斯河；
and the Severn in Wales and England.
以及橫跨威爾斯與英格蘭的塞文河。
'Since we are sort of honouring the rivers, five rivers, that they should get awakened,
'既然我們要表達對這些河流的敬意，這五條河流都應該被喚醒，
and those who drink water out of those rivers, should have the Nabhi by which they should seek God'.
那些飲用那些河川之水的人們，應當具有尋求上帝的臍輪（Nabhi）。'
'And did those Feet in Ancient Time,
遠古時分，雙足是否
Walk upon England's mountains green?'
踏過英格蘭蒼翠的山巒？'
We honour and remember all the Divine Hands that have come before to lay the foundations of the New Jerusalem.
我們榮耀且銘記所有在締造新耶路撒冷根基時降臨的神聖之手。
We remember how Shri Ganesha Himself meditated upon the banks of the River Thames,
我們銘記象神格泥沙親自曾在泰晤士河畔冥想，
and later Shri Adi Guru Dattatreya, whose spiritual followers became the first Druids and the builders of Stonehenge.
後來太初導師錫呂·達陀陀哩耶，其靈性追隨者成為最早的德魯伊和巨石陣的建造者。
Like Blake, in his poem Jerusalem and confirmed by Shri Mataji Herself,
如同布萊克在其詩作《耶路撒冷》中所描述，並由錫呂瑪塔吉親口證實，
we remember how in ancient time, in the first half of the first century AD,
我們記得在遠古時代，公元一世紀前半葉，
sometime between the years 12 and 29, Mother Mary and the youthful Jesus landed in his uncle's merchant ship at Looe on the Cornish coast
大約在西元 12 年至 29 年間，聖母瑪利亞與年輕的耶穌搭乘叔父的商船抵達康沃爾海岸的盧港
and walked all over the West Country of England, vibrating the Earth for generations to come;
並徒步走遍英格蘭西部鄉野，為後世世代代啟迪這片土地；
how Christ planted his staff in the Mother Earth at Wyrral Hill
記載基督如何在威拉爾山將手杖插入大地母親
overlooking Glastonbury Tor, 'Ynys Wydryn, the Agnya chakra of England, and it rooted overnight
俯瞰著格拉斯頓伯里突岩「Ynys Wydryn」——英國的額輪，那手杖在一夜之間生根發芽
and grew into a hawthorn tree that blooms each year at Christmas.
並長成了一株每年聖誕節都會綻放的山楂樹。
How Christ once built there and dedicated a wooden temple in honour of His Mother,
耶穌基督曾在此為祂的母親建造並奉獻了一座木製神廟，
that was worshipped and praised by the patron saint of Wales, St David, centuries later in 540 AD,
這座神廟在數世紀後的公元 540 年受到威爾斯的守護聖人聖大衛的崇敬與讚美，
and even recognised by Augustine, the 6th Century Bishop of Canterbury, as the first church and 'one divinely built by the hands of Christ Himself'.
甚至被 6 世紀坎特伯雷大主教奧古斯丁認可為第一座教堂，且「是由基督親手神聖建造的」。
And how Christ and Mary loosened the stranglehold of druidic power over the heart of the society of Ancient Britons.
而基督和瑪利亞如何解放了德魯伊教對古不列顛社會核心的窒息性掌控
Those same Druids who had by then become corrupt
那些德魯伊教徒此時已墮落腐化
and jealously controlled knowledge and power like high-caste Brahmins with their secret knowledge and rituals.
如高等種姓婆羅門般妒忌地壟斷知識與權力，掌握著秘傳知識與儀式
In 3rd Century Roman Britain, Shri Adi Guru Dattatreya again incarnated as the soldier St Alban,
公元三世紀的羅馬不列顛時期，太初導師錫呂·達陀陀哩耶再度降世為士兵聖奧爾本
from the word 'Alba' meaning white, to protect the spiritual from harm.
從「奧爾本」這個意為白色的詞彙而來，是為了保護靈性免受傷害。
When put on trial for giving sanctuary to a persecuted Christian, he declared to his Roman judges:
當他因庇護受迫害的基督徒而受審時，他向羅馬法官宣告：
'I worship and adore the true and living God who created all things.'
「我敬拜並崇敬創造萬物的真神。」
In Georgian Britain, from 1757 to 1827, Shri Bhairavanath incarnated as William Blake
在喬治亞時期的英國（1757 年至 1827 年間），錫呂·巴爾伐納特降世為威廉·布雷克
to express through all the arts a complete vision of the New Jerusalem to show in unparalleled detail
透過各種藝術形式，完整呈現新耶路撒冷的願景，以無與倫比的細膩手法展現
the spiritual evolution of humankind: how to become the Divine Humanity
人類的靈性進化歷程：如何成就神聖人性
by the awakening of Jerusalem within every human being, the feminine power of the Kundalini.
透過喚醒每個人內在的耶路撒冷——即昆達里尼的母性力量
And so, he both prepared the way and prophesied the coming of Shri Mataji and of Sahaja Yoga,
因此，他既鋪路也預言了錫呂·瑪塔吉和霎哈嘉瑜伽的降臨
foretelling the laying of the foundation stone of the New Jerusalem in Lambeth's Vale at the ashram in Chelsham Road.
預示著將在切爾舍姆路道場的蘭貝斯谷奠立新耶路撒冷的基石。
'It was to be that in England you had to establish Jerusalem.
「耶路撒冷必須在英國建立。」
I need not tell you again and again, how important is England in the play of Divine.
我不需一再告訴你們，英國在神聖劇碼中扮演多麼關鍵的角色。
Those who are realised and have experienced know it that this is the place,
那些已得自覺且親身體驗的人都明白，此地正是
this is the country which has to circulate the spiritual powers all over the world.
這是必須將靈性能量傳播至全球的國度。
The whole of England has to be saved, because if the heart dies the whole universe will die'.
整個英國都必須獲得救贖，因為若心臟停止跳動，整個宇宙也將隨之滅亡。
We remember all the great incarnations that have worked so hard
我們感念所有曾辛勤付出的偉大降世神祈
to lay the spiritual foundations we enjoy today.
為我們奠定了今日得以享用的靈性基石。
We salute them and honour them and pray to them to inspire us in the work of the Divine.
我們向他們致敬、尊崇他們，並祈禱他們啟迪我們完成神聖的工作。
More than anywhere else in the world, over 1,300 stone circles appear all over the British Isles
在世界任何地方都無法比擬的是，整個不列顛群島上散布著超過 1,300 座石圈遺址
dating back to Neolithic times and the very beginnings of agrarian society. None compares with Stonehenge.
這些都可追溯至新石器時代農業社會的萌芽時期。但沒有一座能與巨石陣比肩。
During visits with yogis in the early 1980s, Shri Mataji described Stonehenge as the 'Sahasrara of England',
1980 年代初期與瑜伽修行者會面時，錫呂瑪塔吉曾將巨石陣描述為「英國的頂輪」。
and explained that it manifest the union of the Holy Trinity of the Shiva, Shakti and Ganesha principles.
並解釋它體現了濕婆(父)、神力(母)和象神格泥沙(子)原則的聖三一結合。
It contains a Shiva Lingam
它包含一個濕婆林伽
and the heel stone is a Shri Ganesha stone,
而腳跟石是一座象神石，
while the inner blue stone circle, more of a parabola, represents the Shakti power.
內部的藍色石圈更像是一個拋物線，代表神力的力量。
Some of the stones were described by Shri Mataji as Swayambhus created by the Mother Earth,
有些石頭被錫呂瑪塔吉描述為大地之母創造的自然石(Swayambhus)
While most have been engineered by man, some of the large blue Sarsen stones
雖然大部分都由人工雕琢而成，但部分巨大的藍色沙岩
having been transported over 170 miles away from the Preseli mountains in Pembrokeshire, South Wales.
是從 170 英里外的南威爾斯彭布羅克郡的普瑞斯里山脈運送而來
According to Shri Mataji, Shri Adi Guru Dattareya Himself oversaw the construction.
根據錫呂瑪塔吉的說法，整個建築過程是由太初導師錫呂·達陀陀哩耶親自監督
Apparently, the cross lintels were added much later and actually stopped the flow of vibrations. Relatively few of these lintels remain today.
很明顯，這些橫楣是後來才加上去的，實際上阻止了生命能量的流動。如今這些橫楣留存下來的相對稀少。
Astrologically, the structure is oriented towards the winter solstice at sunset
從占星學的角度來看，這座建築的朝向是日落時的冬至
and the summer solstice at sunrise, and the site is on cardinal ley lines
和日出時的夏至，而且該地點位於重要的能量線上，
that connect it to other sites of great spiritual significance within the British Isles and beyond.
將其連接到不列顛群島內外其他具有重要精神意義的地點。
In fact, the greatest points of intersection between those channels of energy
事實上，這些能量通道之間最大的交會點
occur at Anglesey, in Northwest Wales,
位於威爾斯西北部的安格爾西島、
the Lake District, in Northwest England, with its Castlerigg stone circle,
英國西北部的湖區，那裡有卡斯勒里格石圈、
Glastonbury on the Somerset levels, in Southwest England,
以及英國西南部薩默塞特平原上的格拉斯頓伯里
and most of all at Stonehenge, on Salisbury plain -
尤其在索爾茲伯里平原上的巨石陣——
with the line of St Michael (an aspect of Shri Bhairava)
與錫呂·巴爾伐的一種展現形式交會
also known as the line of Apollo and Athena connecting the Swayambhuh at Skellig Michael, in Ireland,
這條線也被稱為阿波羅與雅典娜之線，連接了愛爾蘭斯凱利格·邁克爾島上的自然石（Swayambhuh）
with St Michael's Mount, in Marazion, Cornwall,
以及康沃爾郡馬拉宰昂的聖米迦勒山
Mont-Saint Michel, in Normandy, France,
法國諾曼第的聖米歇爾山，
Cabella, in Liguria, Italy,
義大利利古里亞的卡貝拉，
Delphi, in Greece,
希臘的德爾斐，
ending at Mount Carmel, the spiritual centre of the Gnostic Essenes, near Jerusalem, in Israel.
最後抵達以色列耶路撒冷附近，諾斯底艾賽尼派的靈性中心——卡梅爾山。
Near to where Shri Mataji once lived at Shudy Camps in Cambridgeshire, is a hill called 'Gog Magog',
距離錫呂瑪塔吉曾經居住的劍橋郡 Shudy Camps 不遠處，有座名為「Gog Magog」的山丘，
which Shri Mataji confirmed was created by people of Indian origin,
錫呂瑪塔吉證實這座山丘是由印度裔先民所建造，
who had migrated there during the time of the Mahabharat to worship the Devi in England.
這些先民是在《摩訶婆羅多》時期遷徙至此，為的是在英國供奉女神。
It was at this time that Shri Anglai Devi was worshipped as the Mother of the English, who in addition to Mother Mary, is none other than Shri Mahalakshmi.
正是在那個時期，人們尊崇 Shri Anglai Devi 為英國之母，而除了聖母瑪利亞之外，她正是摩訶拉希什米的化身。
Shri Samarth Ramdas later discovered Her murti (her form) in the mid-17th century in the Krishna River at Brahmapuri,
聖人薩馬特·拉姆達斯於 17 世紀中葉在馬哈拉施特拉邦的克里希納河畔，巴勒瑪普里發現了她的神像（她的形體），
and established Her temple at Shivaji's fort of Sajjangad, near Satara, in Maharashtra.
並在馬哈拉施特拉邦，薩塔拉附近的希瓦吉堡壘薩占加德建立了她的神廟。
Moving northward through the Pennine mountains the spine of England, we reach Scotland, Alba.
向北穿越英格蘭的脊樑—奔寧山脈，我們抵達蘇格蘭，阿爾巴。
Salutations to the Goddess who abides in Scotland, 'Alba', the Sahasrara of Great Britain,
向駐錫於蘇格蘭「阿爾巴」——大英國頂輪的女神致敬。
the pure white land of Shri Sadashiva, of Lord God Almighty and the holy seat of Shri Shiva Himself,
在雪白純淨的全能主聖地，至高無上的神與濕婆的神聖居所
who resides at Mount Schiehallion, near Aberfeldy in the very geographical centre of Scotland -
祂駐於蘇格蘭地理中心亞伯費爾迪附近的謝赫安嶺
'Sìth Chailleann', the Caledonian mountain of the fairies.
"西思·凱連"——凱爾特傳說中的精靈之山
Shri Mataji commented that, as in the Himalayas, Shri Shiva resides in the North looking southward
錫呂‧瑪塔吉曾說，如同在喜馬拉雅山脈，濕婆駐在北方向南俯瞰
and originally asked the yogis to find an ashram here in Scotland, before eventually settling at Shudy Camps in Cambridgeshire in the mid-1980s.
最初曾請瑜伽士在蘇格蘭這裡尋找一座靜修室，最終在 1980 年代中期選擇定居於劍橋郡的舒迪營地。
Scotland is full of stone circles from Neolithic times, like the Majestic 'Ring of Brodgar', in the Orkney Islands,
蘇格蘭遍布著新石器時代的石圈，例如奧克尼群島上雄偉的「布羅德加之環」，
and vibrated holy islands such as the Isle of Skye, 'An t-Eilean Sgitheanach',
以及充滿生命能量的聖島如「天空之島」，
and Iona, 'Ì Chaluim Chille'.
和「聖科倫巴之島」愛奧納。
Edinburgh itself, 'Dùn Èidean', has seven hills vibrated with strands of Shri Mataji's hair
愛丁堡本身蓋爾語稱作「Dùn Èidean」，七座山丘因錫呂‧瑪塔吉的髮絲而充滿生命能量
and includes the Ganesha Swayambhuh of Arthur’s Seat, 'Suidhe Artair'.
其中包含亞瑟王座的格尼沙自然石
For William Blake, Scotland represented 'Urthona', the mysterious Shiva-like 'Zoa' of inspiration and poetic genius,
對威廉·布雷克而言，蘇格蘭象徵著「烏爾托納」——這位如濕婆般神秘的「生命靈體」，代表著靈感與詩歌天才
the one who tirelessly keeps the Divine Vision in time of trouble and who incarnates as 'Los'
祂在危難時刻始終不渝地守護神聖景象，並降世為「洛斯」
the Divine Artist and Craftsman with his hammer beating out the rhythm of Time,
神聖的藝術家與工匠，用他的鎚擊打出時間的節奏，
taking us beyond the physical, emotional and rational worlds to lead us towards the pure realm of the Spirit.
帶領我們超越物質、情感與理性的世界，邁向純粹靈性的境界。
But more than this, as foretold first by Blake and again emphasised by Shri Mataji Herself,
但不止於此，正如布雷克最初預言，而後錫呂·瑪塔吉再次強調的，
through the pure love of Shiva-Shakti, we celebrate the coming together of all the four chambers of the Heart:
透過神力純淨的愛，我們慶祝心輪四室的完美交融。
England - 'Albion', Scotland - 'Alba', Ireland - 'Éire', and Wales - 'Cymru',
英國 - 「阿爾比恩」，蘇格蘭 - 「阿爾巴」，愛爾蘭 - 「埃里」，威爾斯 - 「西姆魯」，
to form the blessed integrated Heart that heralds the coming of the New Jerusalem, the Golden Age of Heaven on Earth,
共同構成這片蒙恩的整合之心，預示著新耶路撒冷的降臨，那人間天堂的黃金時代，
showering the light of the Supreme Spirit, manifest through the Spirit of all Beings.
傾瀉至高之靈的光輝，透過眾生之靈彰顯神蹟。
May God bless you all,
願上帝保佑你們每一個人。
and bless this country.
並祝福這個國家。
May God bless you.
願上帝保佑你。
Let me enjoy Your feet in my heart,
讓我從心享有您的蓮足，
Let me see Your feet in my heart, O Mother, forever be in my heart,
母親啊，讓我從心看見您的蓮足，願您永駐我心，
Forever, please, reside in my heart.
永遠地，請駐留在我心中。
O Mother, please, stay in my heart.
噢，母親，請永遠駐留在我心中。